7days.ae 2015-05-31

# Privacy Policy - 7DAYS UAE

This privacy policy applies only to this website (the “Site”). If you do not accept this privacy policy, you must not use this Site. 

Collection of Personal Information We collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you complete registration or enquiry forms, submit comments to the Site, participate in message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities or send emails to us. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it. 

Collection of Other Information/Cookies In addition to personal information, we may collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site. The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you first visit the Site. The cookie allows us to identify your computer and find out details about your last visit. Most Internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience with the Site will be as quick or responsive as if you do receive cookies. 

The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not personally identifiable, it includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the Internet e.g. operating system and platform, IP address, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on the Site and geographical location. 

Advertisements on our site are provided by another organisation. Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. 

Use of Your Information 

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which shall include (without limitation): 

• Verifying your identity (for example when you return to the Site) • Personalising your visits to the Site and developing the design and style of the Site to improve the services provided to you • Informing you about the latest changes to the Site, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting • Dealing with, and responding to you about, a comment you have submitted for or on our message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities • Enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using our Email a friend and Share this article facilities • Communicating (and personalising such communication) with you • Informing you if you have been successful in any Site competitions or promotions • Compiling customer reviews • Conducting market research • Carrying out statistical, technical and logistical analysis 

Email Subscription 

If you would like to unsubscribe from recieving emails from us simply click on the ‘Manage my subscription’ or ‘Unsubscribe’ links at the bottom of any of the emails we have sent you in the past. If you do not have access to these emails then please send an email to feedback@7days.ae with the title Unsubscribe. If after having tried either of the above you are still having difficulties please contact us by phone on: 00971 4 283 1317 

Sharing Your Personal Information 

By using the Site, you agree that we may disclose your personal information to any company within the Daily Mail and General Trust plc group of companies. Subject to obtaining your consent, we may also supply personal information about you to third parties. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws and government or regulatory bodies’ lawful requests for information. We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business. Message boards, blogs and other public forums 

The Site makes message boards, blogs and other such user generated content facilities available to users of the Site and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our Site becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information. For more information, please click on the Site’s Terms -http://www.7daysindubai.com/termsandconditions.html Email a friend and Share this article facilities 

When you use these facilities and provide us with personal data (e.g. the name and email address) of a third party, please ensure that you have their consent before giving us their details. 

Safeguards and Security 

No data transmission over the internet can be entirely secure, so we do not guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of the Site. However, we use reasonable endeavours to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorised access or use by using encryption technology. 

Accessing Your Personal Information 

If you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, or have any other queries please write to us (including full details of your request) at: 

Al Sidra Media LLC PO Box 35207 Dubai UAE

We may charge a small administration fee (not exceeding the maximum permitted by law) in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.
